<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>partnerships on Eigh-Ba IBD</title>
    <link>http://mah8.github.io/tags/partnerships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in partnerships on Eigh-Ba IBD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:50:46 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mah8.github.io/tags/partnerships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking New Markets</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/15/unlocking-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:50:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/15/unlocking-post/</guid>
      <description>Expanding your business to new foreign markets can be a fantastic way to grow your customer base and increase profitability. However, entering a foreign market can be daunting, with many risks and challenges to navigate. One way to mitigate those risks and tap into new markets is through long-term partnerships with local companies. In this blog post, we will discuss how partnering with local companies can complement sales channels and networks, allowing you to tap into markets currently out of reach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Perfect Partnership</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/28/fit-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/28/fit-post/</guid>
      <description>Finding the right partnership for your business in new distant markets requires careful evaluation, effective communication, and a deep understanding of the local business landscape. By defining your goals and objectives clearly, researching potential partners carefully, assessing cultural fit, evaluating communication, checking references, negotiating agreements, and collaborating with local experts, you can increase your chances of success and ensure that your partnership is productive and beneficial for all parties involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Expansion, how to prepare</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/24/risks-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/24/risks-post/</guid>
      <description>Expanding a business internationally comes with inherent risks and challenges that must be carefully considered and planned for. To prepare for these risks, it&amp;rsquo;s important to conduct thorough market research, seek legal and financial counsel, develop scalable operations, and carefully manage your brand&amp;rsquo;s reputation. By taking these steps, you can minimize risks and increase your chances of a successful international expansion</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
