<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>partnerships on Eigh-Ba IBD</title>
    <link>http://mah8.github.io/tags/partnerships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in partnerships on Eigh-Ba IBD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 21:29:20 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mah8.github.io/tags/partnerships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Perfect Partnership in new markets</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/28/fit-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/28/fit-post/</guid>
      <description>Expanding your business into new, distant markets can be a challenging and complex process. It requires a deep understanding of the local business landscape, cultural differences, and the ability to navigate regulatory hurdles. One of the most effective ways to successfully enter a new market is to find the right partnership. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore strategies for finding the perfect partnership for your business in new distant markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risks of International Expansion, how to prepare</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/24/risks-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/24/risks-post/</guid>
      <description>Expanding a business internationally can be an exciting opportunity for growth and success, but it also comes with inherent risks and challenges that must be carefully considered and planned for. As a specialized trade magazine, we understand the importance of preparing for these risks to ensure a successful international expansion.
Market Risks One of the primary risks of international expansion is the uncertainty of the new market. Each country has its own unique economic, political, and regulatory environment that can impact the success of your business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
