<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cultural intelligence on Eigh-Ba IBD</title>
    <link>http://mah8.github.io/categories/cultural-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cultural intelligence on Eigh-Ba IBD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mah8.github.io/categories/cultural-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Partnerships in a VUCA World</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/10/vuca-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/10/vuca-post/</guid>
      <description>The modern volatile, uncertain, complex, and ambiguous business landscape prompts many businesses to explore cross-border alliances for competitiveness and sales. These partnerships often involve distant, international partners, adding complexity to the endeavor, but the benetits are plenty if done right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building trust across cultures</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/18/trust-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/18/trust-post/</guid>
      <description>Trust in international business relationships hinges on cultural understanding, effective communication, and appreciation for partners&amp;rsquo; culture. Enhancing cultural intelligence and embracing culturally sensitive tactics helps build lasting cross-border collaborations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CQ - Why is essential for success</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/12/cq-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/12/cq-post/</guid>
      <description>CQ - Why is essential for success In today&amp;rsquo;s globalized economy, businesses are increasingly seeking to expand their operations and enter new markets. However, cross-border business partnerships can be challenging due to cultural differences that can impact communication, negotiation, and decision-making. That&amp;rsquo;s why cultural intelligence is essential for successful cross-border business partnerships.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
