<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cultural intelligence on Eigh-Ba IBD</title>
    <link>http://mah8.github.io/categories/cultural-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cultural intelligence on Eigh-Ba IBD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mah8.github.io/categories/cultural-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Distant partnerships in a VUCA World</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/10/vuca-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/10/vuca-post/</guid>
      <description>Distant partnerships in a VUCA World In today&amp;rsquo;s world, the business landscape is more complex and volatile than ever before. The acronym VUCA (Volatile, Uncertain, Complex, Ambiguous) has become widely used to describe this environment. One consequence of this VUCA world is that many businesses are forming cross-border alliances and partnerships in order to remain competitive and achieve their goals. These alliances and partnerships often involve distant partners who are located in different countries and time zones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building trust across cultures</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/18/trust-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/18/trust-post/</guid>
      <description>Building trust is a critical component of any successful business relationship. However, when it comes to international business relationships, building trust can be particularly challenging due to cultural differences. To build trust across cultures, business professionals must develop cultural intelligence (CQ) and adopt strategies that are sensitive to the cultural norms, values, and practices of their international partners.
One of the key ways to build trust across cultures is to show respect for cultural differences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CQ - Why cultural intelligence is essential for success</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/12/cq-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/12/cq-post/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s globalized economy, businesses are increasingly seeking to expand their operations and enter new markets. However, cross-border business partnerships can be challenging due to cultural differences that can impact communication, negotiation, and decision-making. That&amp;rsquo;s why cultural intelligence is essential for successful cross-border business partnerships.
Cultural intelligence (CQ) is the ability to understand and navigate cultural differences, adapt to different cultural contexts, and effectively work with people from diverse cultural backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
