<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>risks on Eigh-Ba IBD</title>
    <link>http://mah8.github.io/tags/risks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in risks on Eigh-Ba IBD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:50:46 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mah8.github.io/tags/risks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking New Markets</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/15/unlocking-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:50:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/15/unlocking-post/</guid>
      <description>Expanding your business to new foreign markets can be a fantastic way to grow your customer base and increase profitability. However, entering a foreign market can be daunting, with many risks and challenges to navigate. One way to mitigate those risks and tap into new markets is through long-term partnerships with local companies. In this blog post, we will discuss how partnering with local companies can complement sales channels and networks, allowing you to tap into markets currently out of reach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnerships in a VUCA World</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/10/vuca-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/10/vuca-post/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world, the business landscape is more complex and volatile than ever before. The acronym VUCA (Volatile, Uncertain, Complex, Ambiguous) has become widely used to describe this environment. One consequence of this VUCA world is that many businesses are forming cross-border alliances and partnerships in order to remain competitive and achieve their goals. In this post, we will explore the challenges and opportunities presented by distant cross-border business alliances and partnerships in a VUCA world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Expansion, how to prepare</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/24/risks-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/24/risks-post/</guid>
      <description>Expanding a business internationally comes with inherent risks and challenges that must be carefully considered and planned for. To prepare for these risks, it&amp;rsquo;s important to conduct thorough market research, seek legal and financial counsel, develop scalable operations, and carefully manage your brand&amp;rsquo;s reputation. By taking these steps, you can minimize risks and increase your chances of a successful international expansion</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
