<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>risks on Eigh-Ba IBD</title>
    <link>http://mah8.github.io/tags/risks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in risks on Eigh-Ba IBD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mah8.github.io/tags/risks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Distant partnerships in a VUCA World</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/10/vuca-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/10/vuca-post/</guid>
      <description>Distant partnerships in a VUCA World In today&amp;rsquo;s world, the business landscape is more complex and volatile than ever before. The acronym VUCA (Volatile, Uncertain, Complex, Ambiguous) has become widely used to describe this environment. One consequence of this VUCA world is that many businesses are forming cross-border alliances and partnerships in order to remain competitive and achieve their goals. These alliances and partnerships often involve distant partners who are located in different countries and time zones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risks of International Expansion, how to prepare</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/24/risks-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/24/risks-post/</guid>
      <description>Expanding a business internationally can be an exciting opportunity for growth and success, but it also comes with inherent risks and challenges that must be carefully considered and planned for. As a specialized trade magazine, we understand the importance of preparing for these risks to ensure a successful international expansion.
Market Risks One of the primary risks of international expansion is the uncertainty of the new market. Each country has its own unique economic, political, and regulatory environment that can impact the success of your business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
