<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>international expansion on Eigh-Ba IBD</title>
    <link>http://mah8.github.io/categories/international-expansion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in international expansion on Eigh-Ba IBD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mah8.github.io/categories/international-expansion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Distant partnerships in a VUCA World</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/10/vuca-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/03/10/vuca-post/</guid>
      <description>Distant partnerships in a VUCA World In today&amp;rsquo;s world, the business landscape is more complex and volatile than ever before. The acronym VUCA (Volatile, Uncertain, Complex, Ambiguous) has become widely used to describe this environment. One consequence of this VUCA world is that many businesses are forming cross-border alliances and partnerships in order to remain competitive and achieve their goals. These alliances and partnerships often involve distant partners who are located in different countries and time zones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Perfect Partnership in new markets</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/28/fit-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/28/fit-post/</guid>
      <description>Expanding your business into new, distant markets can be a challenging and complex process. It requires a deep understanding of the local business landscape, cultural differences, and the ability to navigate regulatory hurdles. One of the most effective ways to successfully enter a new market is to find the right partnership. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore strategies for finding the perfect partnership for your business in new distant markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building trust across cultures</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/18/trust-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/18/trust-post/</guid>
      <description>Building trust is a critical component of any successful business relationship. However, when it comes to international business relationships, building trust can be particularly challenging due to cultural differences. To build trust across cultures, business professionals must develop cultural intelligence (CQ) and adopt strategies that are sensitive to the cultural norms, values, and practices of their international partners.
One of the key ways to build trust across cultures is to show respect for cultural differences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Cultural Differences</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/02/navigating-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/02/02/navigating-post/</guid>
      <description>Navigating cultural differences is crucial for success in international business. With different cultures come different values, beliefs, and customs, which can significantly impact business interactions. In this blog post, we’ll explore some tips for navigating cultural differences in international business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risks of International Expansion, how to prepare</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/24/risks-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/24/risks-post/</guid>
      <description>Expanding a business internationally can be an exciting opportunity for growth and success, but it also comes with inherent risks and challenges that must be carefully considered and planned for. As a specialized trade magazine, we understand the importance of preparing for these risks to ensure a successful international expansion.
Market Risks One of the primary risks of international expansion is the uncertainty of the new market. Each country has its own unique economic, political, and regulatory environment that can impact the success of your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CQ - Why cultural intelligence is essential for success</title>
      <link>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/12/cq-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mah8.github.io/blog/2023/01/12/cq-post/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s globalized economy, businesses are increasingly seeking to expand their operations and enter new markets. However, cross-border business partnerships can be challenging due to cultural differences that can impact communication, negotiation, and decision-making. That&amp;rsquo;s why cultural intelligence is essential for successful cross-border business partnerships.
Cultural intelligence (CQ) is the ability to understand and navigate cultural differences, adapt to different cultural contexts, and effectively work with people from diverse cultural backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
